<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MSc</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="msc_home">
        "Master of Science in Computer Science, HKU \n\n"

        "The MSc(CompSc) programme is a comprehensive postgraduate study programme provides advanced and in-depth learning in Computer Science. The programme is credit unit based, with courses of both applied and fundamental nature. Students can choose from a comprehensive and diversified study in Computer Science courses or focussed streams of study. Focussed streams of study represent a cohesive collection of related courses that provides both fundamental and in-depth exposure to students in a given ICT domain."

    </string>
    <string name="msc_about_faculty">
        "The Department of Computer Science is committed to high-quality education and training of computing professionals at both the undergraduate and postgraduate levels. At the postgraduate level, we offer two taught programmes based on coursework, the MSc(CompSc) and the MSc(ECom&amp;IComp), as well as the research-based MPhil and PhD programmes.\n\n"

        "The academic staff is active in research and development in a variety of areas including databases, parallel and distributed computing, computer networks, computer graphics, algorithms and complexity, computer vision, multimedia, software engineering, statistical computing, information security and computer forensics, and legal aspects of computing. Some of our research results have been applied to the development of real software and systems. You will have these researchers as your inspiring teachers of the courses in this programme. Here are some of them."
    </string>
</resources>